&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我之前提到了一种神奇的行为，比如
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I referenced a bit earlier a sort of magical behavior like
访问基元值的属性。
accessing properties on primitive values.
记住，您可以访问原始字符串的长度或
Remember, you access a length on a primitive string or
例如，本原数上的一些方法。
some method on a primitive number, for example.
那这是怎么回事？
So how does that work?
我们如何在这里访问某个字符串值的.length？
How is it that we access the .length of some string value here?
此DOM元素值始终是字符串。
This DOM elements value is always a string.
那么我们如何访问.length？
So how do we access that .length?
嗯，原来这叫拳击。
Well, it turns out that's called boxing.
这是一种隐含的强迫。
It's a form of implicit coercion.
在抽象操作中，它不是以相同的方式调用的。
It's not called out in the same way in the abstract operations.
但我认为它在精神上绝对是一种隐含的胁迫。
But I think it absolutely in spirit is an implicit coercion.
它是说你有一个不是物体的东西
It is saying you have this thing that is not an object and
你试图把它当作一个对象来使用。
you're trying to use it as if it is an object.
我，JavaScript，我会很有帮助的，继续把它变成你的对象。
Me, JavaScript I'm gonna be helpful and go ahead and make it into an object for you.
唯一的另一种选择是JavaScript抛出一个异常，该异常表示
The only other option would be for the JavaScript to throw an exception that said
您正在尝试访问原始值的属性。
you're trying to access a property on an primitive value.
我实际上很高兴JavaScript隐含地强制这些原语
I am actually quite happy that JavaScript implicitly coerces these primitives
到它们的对象对应物中，以便我可以访问它们的属性和方法。
into their object counterpart so that I can access properties and methods on them.
我认为这使得代码更加清晰。
I think that makes the code much more clear.
如果我想编写代码，我必须将原语转换为对象
If I wanted to write code where I had to turn a primitive into an object just to
用它，我会去写Java。
use it, I'd go write Java.
这，我认为，是JavaScript的无名英雄之一，
This, I think, is one of the unsung heroes of JavaScript,
它做这个拳击并且做得很好。
that it does this boxing and it does it well.
但这是一种隐含的胁迫。
But it is an implicit coercion.
是吗？&gt；&gt；演讲者2：是在那里吗
Yes? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is that where
这一切都是一个物体的概念是从哪里来的？
this notion of everything is an object comes from?
&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：是的，这正是我在
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is, that's exactly what I meant when I was
在引言中说，人们认为一切都是一个对象。
talking in the intro, that people think that everything's an object.
事实证明，事物可以表现为物体，但是
And it turns out that things can behave as objects, but
但这并不能让他们成为对象。
that doesn't make them an object.
这不是一个物体。
This is not an object.
它是一个原语字符串，其中包含优化，您可以在其中访问
It is a primitive string that has an optimization in it where you can access
一种属性，就像它是一个对象一样。
a property as if it was an object.
所以这些都是在你的程序中发生的强迫的例子。
So these are all examples of coercion that are happening in your programs.
我想说的更重要的一点是，我们是称它们为胁迫还是
And the larger point that I want to make is whether we call them coercion or
我们称它们为转换你曾经存在的每一种语言
we call them conversion every single language in existence that you've ever
编程的必须处理类型转换。
programmed in has to deal with type conversions.
建议你可以写作完全是胡说八道
It is complete nonsense to suggest that you can write
有效合理的JavaScript程序，不需要处理类型转换。
valid reasonable JavaScript programs and not need to deal with type conversion.
你总是会有一个字符串，你需要把它当作一个数字或者
You're always gonna have a string that you need to treat as a number or
需要将其视为布尔值的数字。
a number that you need to treat as a Boolean.
你将不得不处理转换，也就是强制。
You are going to have to deal with conversions, aka coercion.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是绝对必要的，所以，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's absolutely necessary, so,
不管你承认与否你都要用它。
you're gonna use it whether you're admitting it or not.
因为你真的别无选择。
Cuz you really have no choice.